(Howard:)What does that tell you?
(Penny:)You'd be willing to die a horrible death on
the off chance you'd get to second base.
(Bernadette:)We're way past second base.
Right, Howard?
(Howard:)Well, we kind of disagree
about what the bases are.
(Bernadette:)How's your work going, Penny?
Any acting jobs?
(Penny:)The last big thing I did
was this production...
(Penny:)...of Diary of Anne Frank
above a bowling alley.
(Penny:)But I think things
might be turning around pretty soon.
Well, great. How come?
(Penny:)Well, promise you won't
make fun of me?
(Leonard:)Of course.
I would never make fun of you.
(Penny:)Okay, well, I went to this psychic
who told me that if I cut my hair...
...I'm gonna get
a national commercial.
[LAUGHING]
What? Seriously?
(Leonard(laughing):)You're getting career advice
from a psychic?
(Howard:)Good job not making fun of her.
She's not one of those phonies, okay?
She wrote a book, has her own website.
(Leonard:)Oh, gee, why didn't you say so?
They don't just let anyone
have a website.
(Penny:)-Why are you being such a jerk?
-You're surprised?